# Kari McCullough

Benicia, Ca, USA • Open to Remote • (703) 589-8396 • thekarinoelle@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/thekarinoelle • behance.net/thekarinoelle • github.com/karinoelle

#### Skills

Adobe XD

Sketch App

Figma

Adobe Photoshop

Working knowledge of HTML, CSS, WordPress

UI Elements, patterns,

hierarchy

Wireframing, prototyping

Mobile app design

Word, Powerpoint, Excel, Google Drive

#### Education

Career Foundry UI Design Certification 2020-2021

East Carolina University Theater Arts 82 units towards BA

#### My Specialties

Interface Design



**User Flows** 



User Research



Wireframing & Prototypes



# **Qualifications Summary**

UX/UI Designer experienced in user empathy and collaboration. Training as an improviser for eight years in active listening, adapting, and acceptance has helped to recognize user needs for a positive experience. And work with various teams to build on each other's ideas by accepting their offers to explore the possibilities.

## **Projects**

- Designed a native streaming app for iOS and Android by performing a competitor analysis, designing user flows, wireframing, prototyping, and user testing using Figma. <u>View project here: WatchGuide</u>
- Created a responsive vegan recipe web app by conducting user research, creating user personas, defining MVP user flows and wireframing, prototyping, user testing, and creating style guides using Adobe XD. View project here: Tasty Vegan
- Developed a portfolio website by curating design projects, designing a color palette, and user testing using Figma, Atom, Github, HTML, CSS, and Javascript. View website here: Portfolio Website

## Recent Work Experience

### Girls Leading Girls

Soccer Coach, 2019-Present

- Formed a new exercise combining basic soccer training and an improv game to build a healthy group dynamic for a newly formed team of players, increasing their morale and participation by 150%.
- Prototyped an animation of a new soccer training exercise using Figma to share with a coaching staff who require visual aid for clearer communication, resulting in staff satisfaction with the visual aid time and efficient use of practice time.

### **Endgames Improv**

Administrator & Instructor, 2017-2020

 Created and tested a web app prototype using AppSheet to reduce employee time-tracking errors and administration overhead, resulting in the company adopting the clocking system into its standard operating procedures and employee satisfaction.